HI removed, cleaned
and corrected by Lunar Team
Oh, boy, am I glad to see you guys.
We are sorely ill-prepared
for this kind of deal.
Quail hunter's dog found her
this morning about 5:30.
Wasn't meant to be hunting quail,
but he was.
Do we know who she is?
No. Looks familiar though,
so I'm guessing local.
People sure look different when
they're dead though, don't they?
That wound doesn't look fatal.
There's no ligature marks on the neck,
so she wasn't strangled or hung.
- Gums are livid, eyes are hemorrhaged.
- Suffocation.
My bet is it's a meth head from the city
coming in off the interstate.
No, it was a local.
And it was an accident.
Her killer didn't intend her to die this way.
- How so?
- She still has her clothes on.
Her abductor was taking her
to a location that was quiet and private...
...so he could undress her
for a sexual assault.
She made too much noise at the wrong
moment, he tried to keep her quiet...
...and smothered her by mistake.
No good to him now,
so then he dumps her.
In a spot only a local would know.
She's all yours. Thanks for waiting.
Why a sexual motive?
Could be gangs or drugs.
Drug-trade smothering? By who?
The Sesame Street Crips?
There's nothing to say
it isn't just boyfriend trouble.
Could be boyfriend trouble.
Doesn't feel like it though.
- Who is this guy?
- He's a consultant.
You want CBI assistance,
he comes as part of the package.
Consultant, huh?
What, are you clairvoyant or some gizmo?
You got psychic powers?
No, no powers. Had them once.
I mean, I pretended I had them, obviously.
No such thing as psychic powers.
So, what is it you do exactly?
You know Rock, Paper, Scissors?
- I do.
- Play me.
On three.
One, two, three.
Go inside the house.
Go do your homework.
Get your homework started. Go. Go now.
Joe.
Mr. and Mrs. O'Keefe?
I'm Agent Teresa Lisbon,
California Bureau of Investigation.
I'm sorry, we're bringing bad news.
- We found your daughter, Melanie.
- No.
No.
Hi.
Who are you?
My name's Patrick Jane,
I'm with the police.
Is this your sister's room?
Yes.
Did someone kill my sister?
Okay.
She didn't come home from work
the night before last.
She waitresses at
the Shand Creek Winery restaurant.
She was on until 11.
Her car is still parked there,
in the parking lot.
We're always asleep
when she comes home...
...we didn't even know she was missing
until morning.
Called all her friends,
nobody knew where she was.
Nobody had seen her
after she left work that night.
She was all set
to go to college in the fall.
- She won a softball scholarship at UCLA.
- We were worried about her...
...going down to Los Angeles
because you read about all the crime.
Did they do anything to her?
Doesn't appear so. She was fully clothed.
Why would anybody
do something like that?
Oftentimes the first name that pops into
the mother's head is the guilty party.
- Jealous boyfriends, anything like that?
- No.
No. Nothing like that.
- Nothing?
- She was always shy of boys.
She was a good girl.
She took her purity pledge in ninth grade.
And she still wears that ring today.
When did she take the posters down?
- After Christmas.
- Who was on the posters?
Boys with long hair from the TV.
- She didn't like them anymore?
- Said they were for little girls.
Do you know who killed her?
No.
- Are you gonna find out who killed her?
- Me and my colleagues are gonna try.
How?
Looking, listening, asking questions.
When you find him, will you tell me?
Sure. Why?
No reason.
- Rigsby.
- Van Pelt.
You get the fax
from the sheriff's department?
- Yes.
- Run the details through the crime database.
- See if we get any matches. Okay, Van Pelt?
- Will do.
I finished the budget reports. Why don't
I drive down and give you guys a hand?
No, you stay there.
Look, I'll call you if I need you.
She has a lover.
Someone she met
around Christmas at a fair...
...it's either too old, too closely related...
...or too villainous to tell the folks about.
I'd bet on villainy.
And his first name starts with an H.
Explains why she wasn't
wearing her purity ring.
It is the damnedest thing. I was at
the Shand Creek that night on a call...
...round about the same time
that girl was taken.
Drunk wouldn't pay his check.
That is the damnedest thing.
You notice anything that might be useful?
Oh, for crying out loud.
Yeah, when I got there,
I saw a black truck, full-sized...
...taking off out of the other end of that lot
going way too fast.
- He's still inside.
- Nearly went after him too.
What time was that?
Quarter to 12.
Have these woods been checked?
Not to speak of.
You might wanna put
a few man-hours into that.
Uh-huh.
That's, uh... That's her car right there.
You wanna take it?
She worked for us
for three summers in a row.
Lovely girl.
- This is good.
- Yes, it is.
It's unbelievable. And from the parking lot.
I was practically right there.
I can't even think about it.
Try this.
- No, I won't.
- This one's really good.
To your knowledge,
did Melanie ever have any incidents...
- ...with disgruntled coworkers maybe?
- Mm.
- Boyfriend problems?
- No.
Mm, this one is really good. Cardamom?
Yes, and caraway.
And a lot of butter.
- Ha, ha.
- Shh!
No, there's no shame in it. A lot of butter.
That's the great thing about food...
...it's indulgence and necessity in one.
What time did Melanie
leave work that night?
To build a timeline,
we need to know exactly.
Well, I know she took off first...
...but I'd have to check her
timecard to be exact.
It wasn't me by the way.
I have a staff of 20 that'll tell you...
...the only time I leave the kitchen
is to take a leak or yell at a customer.
Ha, ha. Sad but true.
So this is the kitchen,
this is the main prep area...
...and this is where the magic happens.
Hey, attention, Randall, pay it.
My office is this way.
This is a go.
She was by no means a gifted server.
Betty Butterfingers,
that's what we called her.
But she had a good spirit.
She left at 11:25.
- Good night.
- She went out that door.
And that's the last we saw of her.
It's all reservations I assume?
- Credit cards?
- Yes. I can get you a full list.
- Great.
- Oh, Raquel. Come in.
These people are here to help find out
what happened to poor Melanie.
Okay. Good.
You and she were good friends,
weren't you?
Not really. She was okay.
Oh.
Because on her wall at home
she has a picture of you and her together.
That's weird, heh. Huh?
I don't know why she has
a picture of me and her, ma'am.
Maybe she has a secret crush on me.
I don't know.
- What's her boyfriend's name?
- She doesn't have a boyfriend.
That's her thing, right? Purity. No boys.
So who was it
that she cut out of the picture?
- I don't know, sir.
- You were there.
It was Christmas, I was high.
Raquel, this is a murder investigation.
If you protect someone who did this,
you'll do time.
I'm sorry, ma'am, I can't help you.
I would if I could. Swear to God.
Thank you.
- Car's clean.
- Have a chat with Raquel, why don't you?
- I'm gonna go check the credit card receipts.
- Okay.
Give me a minute with her.
She's got a super-low threshold.
No. Nope.
Just stand in the doorway,
pretend you're making a phone call.
No. It's illegal and it's unprofessional.
That's why I need you
to stand in the doorway.
One minute.
Raquel, look at me. Before you fall asleep
tonight, while you're lying in your bed...
...relaxing and slowly drifting
off into sleep...
...I want you to think of me.
Think of me
and imagine that you can fly.
Imagine that you're weightless. You can
float gently into the air if you want to.
Safe and calm and serene.
You can fly away and leave all your
burdens and worries and fears behind you.
Imagine that. What a nice feeling it is.
Next time you see me, I say hello,
you'll remember that feeling...
...and you will want to tell me the truth.
Because when you tell the truth...
...you feel that a heavy weight
has been lifted from your shoulders.
I'll say hello and you will feel
as light as a feather...
...as if you were floating on air.
Why don't you sit here a moment and think
about that before you go back to work?
Whatever.
Your friend's crazy. Can I go now?
Yes.
Worked on the chicken.
Right.
Maybe that's a clue.
"Sorry"?
- Take it to the lab.
- Whoa, whoa. Wait, I got a better idea.
Uh, settle down now, everyone.
Settle down.
These are agents
of the California Bureau of Investigation.
- They wanna talk to you a moment.
- There is nothing to worry about.
We need your help.
- Will you help us?
- Yes.
Yes, absolutely.
We know the identity of Melanie's killer.
The murderer of that poor girl
is in this room.
This note was found in Melanie's locker.
We have strong reason to believe
that whoever wrote this note...
...is the killer.
Yes. Unluckily for that person...
...my colleague, Agent Cho here,
is the bureau's chief graphologist.
Each of you will be giving us
a sample of your handwriting...
...left and right-handed.
Cho will examine these samples
and determine which of you left this note...
...which of you is the killer.
Come on, that's ridiculous.
Randall?
Back it up, don't crowd him.
- Voilà.
- Back up.
Let him breathe. Randall?
Randall, why did you want to
say sorry to Melanie?
- I didn't kill her.
- I didn't say that you did.
I asked why you wanted to
say sorry to her.
Your timecard and your boss say
you left work 10 minutes before Melanie.
You waited for her in the parking lot, right?
Right?
There's no law against waiting.
You waited for her.
- I just wanted to speak to her.
- Nothing wrong with that.
You wanted to speak to her,
then what happened?
I was like, "Hey, Melanie, what's up?"
And we talked.
She didn't leave,
she was smiling and laughing...
...so I figured I was doing pretty good.
So I made my move.
And, um, she wasn't so into it,
which was cool.
Only I know she has
this whole virgin thing happening...
...so I figured that I just
have to be more goal oriented.
She was pretty upset. So I apologized...
- ...for any misunderstanding and I left.
- Bitch.
I got in my car and I drove off
and that was it.
Only I felt like
maybe she would still be mad at me?
And, like, complain?
So when I got into work this morning,
before I knew that she was missing...
...I wrote "Sorry,"
and I put it in her locker.
How long were you in the parking lot
with her? Try and be precise.
Five minutes, six.
Randall tried to kiss Melanie...
...because he thought it was on his account
that she didn't leave.
- But she didn't leave because of Randall...
- She was meeting somebody else.
- Are we gonna see Raquel again?
- She's on her way in now.
- Hey.
- Hey. I did the database search.
- I'm e-mailing the results.
- I'm gonna put you on speaker.
It's not much.
One pop for the brand of silver tape, used
two months ago in Fairfield. An abduction.
- What happened?
- Dolores Sanchez, a female, 22...
...migrant farm laborer. Abducted at
a bus stop, she doesn't know how.
She wakes up on a bed in a motel room
all tied up in duct tape, unharmed.
The cleaners found her.
Never saw her abductors, no suspects.
Fairfield PD concluded
it was a drunken prank.
The complainant, Sanchez,
left town so the case kind of drifted away.
- This is very interesting.
- Let's not go off on tangents already.
Any other correlations?
Uh, yes, actually.
Sanchez is a redhead like O'Keefe.
Uh-huh.
Cool down. It's a common brand of tape,
and there's a quarter million...
- ...redheaded women in California. Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
Just supposing, for fun, that it was
the same guy that did both crimes?
He kidnaps a redheaded girl,
ties her up, takes her to a motel room...
...has her at his mercy, but does nothing.
Month later,
kidnaps another redheaded girl...
...but his planning is not good enough
and he kills her in a panic to keep her quiet.
What does that say?
- He's an idiot.
- He's new to this, and he's conflicted.
He's hungry to do terrible things,
but conscience and his fear tell him not to.
So he's not yet going into this
with the proper focus and planning.
And stuff goes wrong.
Or you're making that up...
...and Melanie was murdered
by her secret lover...
...we can be fairly certain she was meeting
at the exact time of her abduction.
Excuse me, I'm
still here. What would you like me to do?
Uh, call all the motels...
...within 10 miles of Shand Creek.
Find one that had a cash booking...
- ...who didn't show the night of the murder.
- No, let's work the solid leads first.
Crosscheck all full-sized black trucks
with known criminals in the Napa area.
Yes, ma'am.
Look, if the boyfriend angle doesn't work,
we'll look at your trainee psychopath.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I don't know anything
so I can't tell anything.
I told them that.
I told you, I don't know anything.
Have a seat, Miss Garcia.
Thanks.
Hello, Raquel.
Melanie had a thing with Hector Romerez.
He's my second cousin.
I was with him at the fair one time
and we ran into Melanie...
...and then they were like, bam,
Romeo and Juliet.
She was meeting him that night.
- The night she died?
- Yes.
And I didn't tell you
because I'm afraid of him.
The Eight Ball Locos?
He runs all the drugs in Vacaville.
And he's had people killed for way less
than just snitching on him like this, for real.
That was funny. The way she gave
him up so easily like that?
Yeah, it was.
But you were right, huh? Secret lover.
Guess I was wrong about the whole
red-hair-and-duct-tape thing.
- You hypnotized her, didn't you?
- I certainly did not.
Okay, no.
Yes, I did hypnotize her, but...
But nothing.
It's unprofessional and it's illegal.
- It's totally out of bounds.
- That's what I told him.
I was gonna say
you had nothing to do with it, but hey.
You allow him to pull that stuff again,
and you'll be showing visitors...
- ...around the statehouse in a stupid hat.
- Yes ma'am, understood.
Rigsby, I got a hot warrant in Vacaville.
You can get there in an hour, can't you?
Yes, boss. I'll get rolling.
- Bring Van Pelt.
- Yes, bo... For a hot warrant?
Why are you still on the line?
Hey, come on. Let's go.
- They do have a few flavors.
- Strawberry.
- You'd like the strawberry?
- Yeah.
You'd like that one? Here, honey.
Sheriff's Department!
We have a warrant! Open up!
Don't move!
He's out! He's out!
Put your right hand behind your back.
- Stop resisting. Give me your hand.
- Don't move. Don't move.
Boom, out of nowhere.
Guy didn't know what hit him.
So, what were you planning to do
if Lisbon hadn't stopped him?
Oh, I didn't bother to formulate a plan.
I knew she'd stop him.
Cho, Jane, let's move. You two fill out
the paperwork with the staties...
...then get back to Sacramento,
hold the fort.
Yes, boss.
Hector, we're investigating
the murder of Melanie O'Keefe.
Do you know who she was?
She was suffocated
and then stabbed to death...
...and dumped on the side of the road
three nights ago.
We know you and Melanie were lovers.
We know you were planning to meet her
that night.
And we can put your truck
in the Shand Creek parking lot.
I've got enough to charge you with,
Hector.
We just wanna know
your side of the story.
How did you two meet?
Oprah and Dr. Phil here.
I told her this is how it was going to end.
Only it was going to be me that died...
...and her sitting here with dumb cops
asking dumb questions.
"Why was a respectable girl like you...
...with a thug like Hector Romerez?"
Why was she?
You wouldn't understand.
Sure, she would.
All women understand
the charm of a violent man.
What we had was special.
Ah.
You made her feel like a captured princess
instead of a small-town choir nerd.
And she made you feel like a dashing pirate
instead of what you are.
A sort of a bad-tempered pharmacist.
Funny man.
Ése, those pirates back then?
They were just banging
like anybody else today.
A pirate is exactly what I am.
And she was a princess.
She was.
What happened that night?
We were supposed to meet
at 11:30 at the restaurant.
I got there 10 minutes late
and she hadn't come out yet.
I waited for a few minutes and I left.
I'm impatient.
I was angry.
I will always hate myself for that.
I left her to be killed...
...because I don't wait for nobody.
That's a noble admission, Hector.
How did you feel about the fact
she was going to college in the fall?
I was proud...
...and happy for her.
- She was leaving you behind.
- I wanted her to leave me behind.
I wanted her far away.
I told her, "Go to L.A.
and don't come back for nothing."
He's telling the truth.
You're trying to be contrary.
You read his sheet?
Hear what he said?
He's a good actor.
It was you who thought it was him.
I said Melanie had a secret lover,
I didn't say he killed her.
If it wasn't him, then who was it?
If you say "A man who likes red hair
and silver duct tape," I'll scream.
- I don't want you to scream.
- Look, you have your reasons, I understand.
But you're seeing more than what's actually
there. You have a tendency to do that.
Not every murder is a secret
inside of a secret inside of a secret.
- There's not always a hidden pattern.
- Not always, but sometimes.
Sometimes the obvious guy did it.
Most of the time, the obvious guy did it.
Look at the timeline.
Hector's admitted he was in the parking lot
for 10 minutes, give or take.
There's wasn't enough time for
anybody else to have entered the lot...
...abducted Melanie and driven away.
It was Hector.
You're right, there's no time.
Hey, Frankie.
So, uh, show me.
Show you what?
Your gun.
- I don't have a gun.
- No?
- Hello?
- Hey, Van Pelt.
- Hey.
- Uh, Lisbon changed her mind.
She wants you to check out
those motels like I said.
- The motels?
- Looking for one...
...with a no-show cash booking
that night.
"Cover all the bases," she says.
She's right here
if you want a word with her.
- Oh, that's okay. But listen...
- Call me first if you get anything.
No gun, huh?
What were you gonna kill Hector with,
a knife?
Oh.
That should work. Just, uh...
...put it away.
What if it turns out that Hector
isn't the man that killed your sister?
Isn't he?
We don't know that yet.
You don't have to worry about that...
...that's for us to work out.
You need to be here for your family.
And leave the vengeance part to us.
When you find who did it for sure...
...will you kill him?
No, I won't kill him,
but I'll make him very sorry.
I have a daughter
who would be about your age...
...if I hadn't caused her death.
Her and her mother.
How?
Out of arrogance, stupidity.
I made an evil man very angry
and he killed them to teach me a lesson.
To make me sorry for what I'd done.
And I am sorry.
Being sorry is a far worse punishment
than being dead. Everybody dies...
...very few people ever feel truly sorry
for the bad things they've done.
It hurts.
Van Pelt, what do you got?
Microwave, spa tub,
and premium cable in every unit.
Special rates for state
and federal employees.
- What did he look like, this man?
- Big.
With a hat and sunglasses,
and a thick beard like a Sikh.
- Ha, an absurd disguise, in other words.
- Ridiculous.
I run a motel, I don't care who you are.
He bought a good beard for nothing.
Then that night he doesn't show.
So I remembered him
when your nice young lady called.
Uh, no disrespect,
but, uh. your maid isn't very thorough.
No, she's most thorough.
She cleans here tomorrow.
- For monthly rentals she...
- Monthly?
Yes, she comes every third day.
So he's been here recently,
in the last two days.
- The chips would imply this, yes?
- Yes, they would.
This?
Those are not ours.
He's coming back.
Okay. Thank you.
Nice work.
Hey.
Listen, I don't wanna make you mad,
but I found something interesting.
- I want you to take a look at it.
- You can't make me mad.
Go ahead. What did you find?
You first. Who made you so happy?
Forensics. There's substantial
traces of Melanie's blood...
...on the seat of Hector's truck.
- Oh. So happy day.
- Yeah.
Now I'm gonna go and see
what Hector has to say about it.
What did you find?
Oh, uh, it can wait.
Blood?
Yes.
Last time I saw her, two weeks ago...
...she was disrespectful...
...so I had to tune her up.
She got a bloody nose.
Was physical abuse a normal
occurrence in you relationship...
...or is this more of a recent thing?
She chose me.
She wanted to know
where the edges are.
I showed her.
Go ahead, say it.
- I think he's telling the truth.
- I disagree. I'm charging him.
No, yes, good.
That's good, you go ahead.
You've got more than enough evidence.
Whoops, I nearly forgot.
Okay, tell me. What did you find?
Telling you won't do, I have to show you.
Hi. Uh, I made a booking for two
for this afternoon.
Could you put us on the terrace?
It's more romantic.
Thanks.
Yeah, Patrick. Lovely. See you then.
Don't fret.
I wouldn't seduce you over a meal.
That would be very sophomoric.
I didn't think you were
trying to seduce me.
Come on. How could that thought
not have entered your head?
Your denial that it did intrigues me.
Bite me.
What is this?
That's Van Pelt. What is she doing?
This a live feed from
the Shand Creek restaurant.
And this is how we're gonna
catch Melanie's killer.
Say again.
Nothing.
Oh, I see you.
- How do I look?
- Good. You look good.
I meant, can you see the wire?
Oh, um...
Uh, nope. Nope.
The killer plans to bring his victim
back to this room.
When he does, we're gonna be here
to greet him. How sweet is that?
This is all a big elaborate joke
you're gonna apologize for now. Yes?
Whoever killed Melanie
had to be there at Shand Creek.
Your timeline proves it. There's no way
anyone else could have done it.
One of the 20 people there that night
killed Melanie.
All 20 of those people are there now, today.
Including the killer.
And he's gonna try it again today?
- Come on.
- No, no, yes.
Yes, that's just the point.
Yes, he is gonna try again.
He's planning on it.
And he's gonna try again today
because we're gonna make him try again...
...because he's not
in control of his desires.
He's been thinking of nothing else
but this perverse craving of his.
He's gotten so close,
he's desperate to go all the way.
All we need to do is present him
with something he can't resist.
Something that he will jump at
and damn the consequences.
Give it a try.
If I'm wrong, there's no harm done.
- It's fusion.
- Confusion.
Up to me,
make it a cheeseburger every time.
Oh, me too. With onion rings.
- Let's do it.
- Not yet.
- Why not?
- This is actually quite good.
Ow.
You're meant to shout at me and leave.
Now you've gone too far.
I hate you!
- Smooth work.
- Don't.
- Can I call you a cab?
- No, thank you. I need a walk.
I have a number for a cab if I need one.
- Thank you for a delicious meal.
- Oh, you're so welcome.
I just left the restaurant.
I'm heading toward the main road now.
Whoa, sorry, miss, I didn't see you there.
I was just, uh...
- You okay?
- Oh, sure, absolutely.
Just scared me a little.
He wasn't...
What the hell is he doing there?
- He was there.
- Ah...
He was there that night.
Going for a stroll?
Fresh air.
Only you need to be careful.
We've been looking for a murderer
on the loose around here.
Yeah, went after a girl just like you.
- Red hair and all.
- No kidding?
Yeah. I'll drive you up to the main road.
Oh, thank you, but...
Oh, no trouble really.
My car's just over here on the side.
- Please advise.
- Keep it rolling.
I beg your pardon?
I'm not used to wearing these shoes.
Are you, uh, out here alone?
I had an argument with my date.
I'm sorry to hear that.
If you were my date I wouldn't...
I wouldn't argue.
A pretty lady like yourself.
My car's just right over here.
- It's okay, I'll walk.
- Wait. No. I won't let you.
Really, ma'am. Really,
I don't feel comfortable letting you go.
Really, I'm fine.
I think you're intoxicated.
- I am not.
- Get your hands off her.
What the hell's the matter with you?
You're under arrest.
- No, you're under arrest, you...
- Rigsby, calm down.
Cho? Is this clown one of yours?
- What the hell is going on here?
- Sheriff, everything okay?
Well, yeah, now it is.
Suppose so. Barely.
- Everything's funny.
- Well, if you try.
I mean, come on, that was pretty funny.
Strange though.
I was sure the chef would bite.
- There's still a chance he could show up.
- The chef? Malcolm?
Why do you think it's him?
He uses way too much butter.
- Say...?
- He's a gluttonous baby. He's self indulgent.
- He wants what he wants and he takes it.
- Too much butter.
- Yeah.
- It's fascinating, the way your mind works.
One thing, Malcolm was in the kitchen
with 20 people...
...when Melanie was taken.
- He couldn't have done it.
- Hang on.
There's a way he could...
Forgive me if I can't stay for more of
your theorizing, but I've gotta go see...
...if I can save your colleagues from getting
formal complaints in their files.
Hey. Yeah, I'll be right there.
Uh-huh.
No, I know where it is.
Okay.
Okay. Right here.
That's good. That's good.
You're good. You're good.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay. Good.
Quiet, quiet. Shh.
Hey, hey. Shh.
Okay.
- Okay, help me put this on the bed.
- Okay.
Stop, think, do not move.
Whatever you do, do not move.
- What?
- Do not move.
Hey! Malcolm.
Stop. Come back here. Stop.
- What are you doing here?
- Think. Think.
- Does it matter? I'm here.
This place is surrounded
by police and CBI agents.
Oh, no.
He's lying. They would be up here
arresting us by now if they were here.
SWAT. They're waiting on SWAT.
There's no way out of this.
There's nobody.
Let's just kill them and get out of here.
Whoa, whoa, listen to me.
You can walk away from all of this.
No disrespect,
but you're both clinically insane.
You're not gonna go to prison,
you'll go to a hospital...
- ...then you can walk away.
- Shut up. Just shut up.
I'm trying to think.
- Oh, now he's trying to think.
- Don't pretend you didn't want this.
- You wanted it just as much as me.
- Malcolm, I told you we didn't have time.
- I swear to God, one more word out of you...
- Don't you point that at me.
Police!
- Put the gun down!
- No.
Okay.
Come on.
It's okay.
You're gonna be fine, all right?
Here, come on.
It's okay.
We're gonna get you out of here.
I don't get it.
She actually enjoyed helping him kill.
One crazy evil person I understand,
but two? Husband and wife?
Marriage is supposed to be
a sacred, loving thing.
Ah, they were soul mates
in their own strange way.
Let's go.